We'll see who uses a bulb now!
Welcome one...
Welcome all...
Here's Sitabo...
And this one's Gulabo...
She comes with a 'Hazratganj' tag.
And this one's landed from 'Aminabad,
Gadbadjhala'...
And all she wants is to lose herself
in the lanes of 'Chandni Chowk'.
Smart is she.
And clever is she.
The battle is set,
The lines are drawn, Seething in anger,
Gulabo fights,
Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
When the village gathered for a feast...
- Here you go.
- Hmm.
- Begum!
- Yes?
Check these out once... Will you?
Wait a bit, mister.
The battle is set, The lines are drawn,
Seething in anger,
Gulabo fights,
Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
The battle is set, The lines are drawn,
Seething in anger,
Gulabo fights,
Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
The battle is set, The lines are drawn,
Seething in anger,
Payal... Neetu...
Gulabo fights, Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
Payal... Neetu... The battle is set,
The lines are drawn, Seething in anger,
What on earth is going on?
I've been around the
whole town looking for you two...
...and here you are,
embarrassing the family name!
C'mmon missies,
out of here for shame sake.
And you, Mirza,
only a douche bag like you would...
...make my little girls dance
on the streets. I swear if you ever...
There you go again, with your tongue...
...moving faster than
a pickpocket's scissors.
Now if I start using mine,
you wouldn't know where to run.
Spare me your nonsense
and give me my share of pennies.
- Oh forget it, he's the greediest man alive.
- Hah...! Never.
Yeah am fine being greedy.
Ya what more can an old sourpuss be.
I'll eat milk pudding with
saffron extracts and won't share.
Greedy, yeah.
Go to hell!
Twenty rupees...
Stop dropping it on my forehead!
Well I'm not doing it on purpose...
sit straight then, will you?
Get off from here...
Don't you stain my face!
Now who's lit this
bulb early in the morning?
Switch it off!
Mumbling...
- Tch... what're you doing, Begum?
- I'm just wiping-
This'll dry up in no time.
It's April for god sake!
-And when did April come?
How the hell does it matter?
Payal, set up Dadda's tiffin.
Amongst all these things... that huge bucket...
those leather chappals... goats...
...all that got stolen was my damn bulb?
His bicycle bell is missing too.
To hell with your bell!
- My bell!
- Oh just ignore this gobshite and get me some tea.
My bulb got stolen and
you're calling me names? Really?
He's crying as if he's lost
all his goddamn family wealth.
He doesn't even have
a face of a wealthy man!
Remember the day Nehru ji came,
those petty thieves were all
over the town plaguing it like rats...
...must be one of them who stole his bulb.
Bang on, Begum!
He's a plagued rat of a thief
who's been stealing off us...
...and making a measly penny or two.
Well he better watch out
'cause I won't spare him.
Why are you forever stuck to the TV?
Go study.
I'm done with my home work...
moreover, it's a holiday.
So? All the more reason to study... uh...
What grade are you in?
Three.
Three? But I've been paying
that damn fee for years!
Brother!
What?
I want to take up a job.
Get done with your grade 12 first.
I'm in the final year of undergrads.
I'd told her to let you know.
What grade are you in?
Eighth.
C'mmon you guys are not
allowed to grow up that fast!
Your brother is not a rich dude yet.
So there's no point talking to him!
As for me, marriage is not my thing...
I'd much rather earn my own salary
and live respectfully...
...in any case,
I'm living in this home of ours.
Yeah but we don't own it...
it's a rented one.
Rent? We've grabbed it!
What rubbish!
That's what Uncle Mirza
goes around saying it to everyone.
Mirza needs to be dug up
in this mansion.
Are you nuts?!
Your tenant Baankey Rastogi,
he's a daft pillock!
Do you really reckon that he, an owner
of a wheat mill in the main market...
...won't have money to pay a higher rent?
Are you asking me this or telling me?
Umm... no I am just saying.
Oh ok, just saying.
That where on earth can one rent
out a house for just 30 rupees?
You won't stop grating on my nerves,
will you?
And only if you were less thick...
...you'd remember
he hasn't paid up for last three months.
Of course I know his story.
His aunt died, father died.
He's still stuck around
like a blood-sucking leech.
The day Begum dies...
...I swear to her grave, I am going
to throw out these roaches of tenants...
...who are infesting my home
and then that mansion...
It'll be yours...
Yeah... only mine.
Say that again...
Mansion will be yours!
Mansion will be mine!
There are five of us
staying in a pigeonhole, Fauzia...
...a small curtained section in the kitchen
is where my mom and sisters bathe...
...and we share the toilet
with Mishraji's family...
...how do I even think of getting married?
When did I even ask for marriage?
But I didn't know you were this poor...
I mean, I thought
staying in FATIMA MAHAL...
...you must be of some rich lineage.
For god sake can you
all not be after that mansion?
I'm not after anything, okay?
Pity you're not the landlord but
there's no need to get so cheesed off.
I'm not getting cheesed off!
Nor do I fancy being the landlord
of that godforsaken dilapidated mansion...
One kick and there
won't be any of it left.
Fine... kick it and stop blabbering... and
just don't get cheesed off...
I am not cheesed off, ok?
It's 4 pm already, sir...
Wait, don't open yet...
I'll see you next week...
...with that chocolate biscuit...
I'm not that poor that I can't buy
a damn chocolate biscuit for you.
It's late...
See you.
Yeah.
Bhaiyya,
this weighing scale is faulty.
What do you expect me to do? Sit on it?
How about paying up for last two months?
Of course I will.
Then do that first!!
What you doing here like a snoopy
sewer rat, looking for breadcrumbs... huh?
Are you increasing the
rent from this month or next?
'Cause your trashy scoofer
existence is getting unbearable you see.
Now what can I say
about your tolerance level.
As for rent...
...this is what it is, take it
or leave it and just so you know,
we're never vacating this place.
Goodnight!
Don't you dare come between
me and my mansion! Or else...
With one leg already in grave,
are you threatening me?
Look I'll just call
the university goons...
...and all your dreams of mansion
will turn into a nightmare...
So just chill.
Oh I'll show you what a nightmare is!
Neetu... go shower now!
Always wasting time.
What?
Parking slip, 50 rupees everyday.
House tax has increased...
Are you a twit? Or you think I am one?
Now move...
No, I won't let you.
Gawd... tch... am getting late
for work... move...!
Then just pay up and take your bike...
But you haven't charged
a penny from Sayyad and Mishraji...
Even they have their bicycles
and scooter parked here.
Yeah but they're not the ones
who pay 30 bucks as house rent!
Just back off,
Mirza, and play with those goats there...
...you've no idea what I can do to you.
Oh really?
The day I throw you outta here...
...lock stock and barrel...
you'll land in hell Mister...
Not even a dog will come and
piss on your face... we'll see then.
Am not scared of anyone...
This is my mansion...
Not your damn parking... is that clear?
Ya ya I got scared.
This is my mansion...
Dare you come again with your bike.
You want to grab my house...
dare you even think...
- C'mmon... show me... anyone...?
- Mirza, Baankey is gone!
-I'll throw all of you outta here...
Just the cleaning of this
chandelier would be 500 bucks...
...and then the bulb etc...
It's antique so nothing
less than 2000 rupees.
It's all glasswork... one thousand.
One thousand?
- Or nothing...
- Tch... uh... wait...
Okay one thousand it is...
Go ahead quietly.
Careful...
I need a minute with her...
She's up in flames...
Let him in...
Umm... Begum... my this month's
allowance is all spent...
I was wondering if I could get...
What about the rent from the tenants...
Who's going to get that...?
Oh leave that on me...
I'll get the rent out of those idiots...
There's some lose currency in that box...
...make do with that for now.
Sure...
And then for a few days
just stay out of my sight...
Sure... sure...
- How much...?
- 20 bucks...
That's it?!
Where is Mirza now?
Hasn't come out of
Uncle Sayyad's room yet...
Ok, keep at it...
Ya, he's out.
Where is he going next...?
Coming here!
Keep a watch.
Oh he's almost here.
Quick... get here...
C'mmon... fast... give that cold strip...
Lie down...
Uh... am here... that's the rent receipt...
What happened... fever?
Since two days and I don't
even have money to buy medicines...
...please don't ask for the rent today...
This month too!
Hey, it's not as if
your wheat mill has shut down...
Ya, but the wheat produce got ruined.
So no one's coming to get the flour...
There's not a morsel at home, Baankey...
We'll have to sell off this mixer...
Yeah... how else to feed your sisters...
That's a microwave.
Food warmer...
Yesterday the rice dish
got heated up in just 2 minutes...
Evidently the crooks are partying...
...well then I must provide the roast.
Couldn't you keep your trap shut?
Brainless...
Now let's see how you eat
your rice dish... heated up!
What's with this power cut?!
Go check it out!
Am sure it's Mirza again!
Now aren't you gonna
leave that throne Mishra ji?
Am not sitting on a throne...
Third time since morning...
Wait...
And you carry those cheap
magazines inside Mishraji...?
What happened?
Did you fall down?
- No... Then?
- Uncle Mirza... he...
What did he do?
I was cutting mangoes for 'Daadi Bi'...
...from that I ate a piece or two...
suddenly Mirza started screaming...
...that brother has grabbed the
house and sister is grabbing mangoes.
And he made me spit out
whatever I had in my mouth...
Alright stop crying...
...get back to home...
Mirza needs to explain this...
Mishraji are you coming out or...
- What fell down?
- What happened?!
What the hell did you do Baankey?
...you'll kill me...
What happened, brother?
How did this fall...?
Was that a bomb blast...?
This wall fell down!
How did this happen?
What are you doing here... go away...
Mishraji... where are you...?
See what Baankey has done...
I just kept my hand there and...
was an old wall anyway...
What did you do, Baankey?
He's been in there for an hour!!
Just because you ride a bike,
you think you can hit the wall?
I don't get the connection!
My time slot is at 8 every morning...
I was here but he's
been inside for an hour...
That too his third time!
On top it he carries newspapers!
We've already fixed our slots so...
Why should he get more than 15 minutes?
Who'll repair this wall now?
What happened, Sheikhu?
Toilet...
God knows what he
does for an hour inside!
Uh oh... Mirza is coming here...
Listen... wait... wait...
let me sort it out first.
I'm going.
No you can't.
These are old
bricks... obviously it had to...
No... no...
I am asking how did it collapse?
I just touched it with my foot
and it came down...
When you don't get things repaired!
- Move aside!
- Wait!
Huh... you think you'll do
the damage and I'll let you go?
Now you'll get this wall done...
Never! Your mansion,
your problem... now get off my way...
I won't... either you increase
the rent or vacate the place...
Sucking on my blood, like a leech.
Don't scream or you'll get an attack...
...and if you pass away before Begum...
imagine what'll happen to this mansion...
You have 24 hours to repair this...
Even if I have 24 years,
I won't do it... you're the landlord... so...
Yeah I am the landlord...
one with the lineage... so!
And I care a damn about it!
That's not fair Mirza...
he just pays 30 bucks...
...and we pay 70.
Which latrine are we going to use now?
We'll use theirs, the 70 rupee tenants!
And Mirza has such a huge mansion...
...am sure we can find many
hidden corners to defecate...
Move...
Oh! He left.
Broke the wall...
That's it... it's all locked now...
no one uses my toilets...
Brother... brother...
What is it...?
I need to use the washroom...
Get up...
Go downstairs... am awake...
Mirza has locked up every toilet...
and he's sleeping right outside...
Please wake up!
Where is he?
Here...
Let's see.
Call Mishraji... quick...
Mirza... how come you landed here...?
Ya... stop.
He picked up my bed and threw me
out of my house while I was sleeping...
He's locked the toilets... my three sisters...
my mother... are they supposed to go out in the open?
One second... relax...
Sir... why did he throw me out...
Listen to me... till the time
the toilet wall is not made,
you'll have to provide
alternate toilets for the women...
No, why should I? He broke the wall...
My fancy toilets are not
for pedestrians like him...
But he's your tenant... and...
And whatever damages happen,
water electricity expenses...
...they all have to be
borne by the landlord...
...we've been paying the rent
for last 70 years...
How did the wall collapse?
How do I know...
...I wasn't sitting inside
the brick that I would know...
...how it broke.
Just see what a doped out
uncivilized obnoxious guy he is!
My 100 year old mansion...
won't let then grab it.
Who's grabbing it...?
And we're discussing the toilet...
not mansion...
So keep your trap shut.
Guys, can we focus on the wall?
Who's going to repair it...?
- Who are these people?
- Mirza or Baankey?
Uh... tch... look Uncle,
these tenants have been staying for years...
...so you can't just throw them out.
You can't throw us out!
Stop being a buffoon...
Because you're a tenant,
you'll never become a landlord even if you've
been staying for 100 years in the same house.
Never ever!
And for any further information,
go to the civil courts...
...this matter belongs there,
not with the police...
Get out now...
That I'm useless...
I repeat... that I'm useless.
I've proven it long back.
I haven't come across a
bigger scoundrel than Baankey...
...he's eyeing your mansion.
And the police maintains the matter
belongs to the civil court...
...and that old woman...
that witch from the dungeons...
...she's also refusing to die...
Have faith in God Mirza...
Begum will die this winter...
Are you sure she'll die...?
Of course!
See what I am saying
is these tenants of yours...
...should pay at least 500 bucks each.
I mean that is the going market rate...
I'll look for a lawyer...
but you stay with that thought...
How much is 2,500 multiplied by 12?
Ummm... 5 by 12 is 60... and...
- 30,000
- What?
30,000
- 30,000? Really?!
- How much is this? - 90 rupees.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah... I'm fine... I'm fine...
- Get him up.
- I'm fine.
30,000?!
Yes... yes... are you okay?
Give me your hand.
Sit, relax.
Sit here... Relax.
30,000?!
Hey... excuse me... what are you doing?
Am talking to you... here, this side.
Can't you see am making a pudding...
How can you take pictures
without permission? Stop it.
Do you take permission
to click historical monuments?
And I don't even see any board
here that prohibits photography...
Don't act smart... I stay here...
...one whack from me,
you'll be on the ground on all fours...
Look Mister,
to begin with, mind your language,
because as per the orders
of the Supreme court,
no matter how long you
may've grabbed the house for...
...you don't have any rights
on the house...
Once a tenant always a tenant.
And who the hell are you?
Lawyer? Police? Army?
I am archeology!
In charge of the ruins... and that you're
a duffer, it's evident from your face.
Am not such a duffer that
you'd fool me with a candy.
Supreme court is in Delhi
and this is Lucknow...
Here, might is right... so get outta here...
right away... jump off that damn tree...
Why are you still sitting
there like a monkey?
I won't be able to jump.
Come down just as you climbed up.
I need help... you see... I've arthritis.
Here...
Doctor says...
...getting down is more difficult
for the knees than climbing up...
And... a... that toilet wall...
you haven't got it repaired, right?
No... why?
Just do as I say...
I am Gyanesh Shukla...
and right now I am in a bit of a hurry...
I'll speak to you later.
Rickshaw!
But you stay in touch.
Come on, hurry up!
Aliganj.
Bye.
For example Mohenjo-daro and Harappa...
So these places were dug up
and whatever stuff came out...
...whatever glass bowls...spoon etc.
The archaeology guys take it away
and display it in museums.
Sometimes, if need be,
they take away the place itself.
And convert it into a museum.
What happened brother...
why are you staring blank?
Looks like brother didn't get it...
There is nothing to not understand...
All I am thinking is we don't have
any such bowls or spoons...
...nor is Mohenjo-daro
in Lucknow district...
Just wondering.
Whats' there to be blank!
Why don't you take your grade 12 exam...
Don't worry we'll help you study...
Well, this is in grade 10 syllabus.
Ya so we'll help you
with grade 10 as well...
That's it... stop here...
Please wait here till I come back.
Are you Mirza?
Uh hmm...
I'm official... archaeology... move.
- Excuse me...
- Where are you going inside...?
I am Gyanesh Shukla.
Baankey knows me.
What are you doing?
You haven't got that
wall repaired, right?
Which one?
The toilet wall you idiot...
- Who the hell are you... get me some tea...
- Go, you go...
- Photo?
- Because I am archaeology.
What?
For the records.
Why are you going there...?
You can't go there...
It's the women's section.
Your mother is still alive?
- Who is that?
- No idea.
Come please...
Look today is a Sunday and I like
to do all the official conversations...
...on working day,
so see you another day...
How the hell did this mansion slip out...
Huh?
Nothing... doesn't matter.
Just wait for an
official letter now...
The fun is about to begin.
Huh?
Let's go.
Who sent him to my mansion...?
How dare he get here... has
to be one of these idiots.
- Send these to Guptaji
- So you called Gyanesh, didn't you?
What? Did he come again?
That means you only called him...
Are you out of your mind...
Why would I call him...
I'm certain it has to be you.
How else did he come to know
about the toilet wall...?
I'm not the only one
who stays in that house...
Anybody could have called him.
Oh you are such a fox!
Oh well... then you are
a broken bone of an anaconda...
Go... wipe your filthy
face, you rotten mongoose...
- Oh you want to?
- Yes!
C'mmon... try me... you lousy lowly man.
Keep that back.
Don't you dare come close.
Huh! I'll do what I feel like.
Weirdo!
I'll see you tomorrow.
What happened?
It's okay... come.
Is everything okay?
Have you lost it?
Or do you suffer from night blindness
that you cannot see what's going on?
Mirza has sent you, right?
Ya he's the third guy, so?!
What's your problem...?
I didn't enjoy with the others...
Am I really the third one?
Looks like your male ego
has been squashed like a lemon.
In that case you can leave now...
- Obviously I'm not going to hang around here.
- Yeah get lost.
Strange woman?!
Get lost!
Keep your hands off me!
What?!
Government official? He came again?!
That archaeology fellow?
I smell trouble.
Look if any government guy comes,
you'll tell me first... is that clear?
You'll get your 50 bucks...
What are you staring at?
Don't you have to get to school?
Yes...
Why've you worn my top?
I couldn't find my top.
Wait... wait...
get off the rickshaw... get off.
Don't do that Mirza.
Oh you mind your own business.
They've no penny for rent but
they've all the money for luxuries... huh.
Come.
Are you Christopher?
Eh... Pandey Ji...
Christopher Clarke.
I specialize in getting house vacated
...and also in getting it nabbed.
I mean how do I trust you...?
Trust?
Look sir, I speak
in English at home.
I eat lunch and dinner for food.
If you have ever heard of that
famous builder in the city, Mun Mun ji.
Well I am very close to him.
And I am not sitting here in this library
to read some useless novel.
I'm here to make points because
I have to get a house nabbed.
Understood?
Mishra... look after this please.
I'll see you later.
Let's go.
And you don't have
to get the house nabbed.
You've to get your house vacated, right?
It's not some property...
It's my mansion.
I know I know it's a mansion.
Here.
- But in legal language it's called property.
- Ok.
And there is not just one
but many property laws.
We will write a plea
and submit it in the court.
We'll give evidence.
Sit please.
They'll get the notice
and the house will be vacated.
Is it that simple?
Of course...
I just need property papers.
Huh?
Papers?
Yeah. Documentation.
All the records that have been...
...maintained between
the landlord and the tenant.
Those papers...
Pandeyji mentioned that...
...the property is in the name
of your wife and now she is no more.
No no she hasn't died.
That's what I'm waiting for.
Look the mansion is mine.
It's just that it's not on my name yet.
Oh... ok... ok.
There is yet another problem.
What?
That archaeology fellow has
also started intruding in between.
Why would an archaeology guy be interested
in a 3 or 4 bedroom property...?
I don't get it.
I have been telling you
that it is a mansion.
- Not some tiny house.
- You mean a real mansion?
Yes, which Begum got from
her father and he got from his father.
Oh... now I get it.
What was that 'oh' for?
You see the day Begum dies.
There'll be at least 50 more greedy guys
knocking on your doorstep... overnight.
Are you getting me?
That is exactly why
I did not have any child.
So that this mansion remains only mine.
For such properties,
even kids get born overnight.
Such mansions don't have
single clear ownership ever.
So you need to find out who is dead,
who is alive.
Can't sit around any more, 'Sherlock...'
Sherlock?
Yes, Sherlock!
Who's dead... who's alive.
Where do I get this?
I'll have to ask Begum.
Who's dead... who's alive.
This one is my eldest sister.
The one with the dripping nose.
She should be dead by now?
I mean who all are alive...?
I don't really remember...
few of them are alive... few, dead.
This one looks quite old.
By that logic, you too are old
and should be dead by now.
Why are you alive?!
So who all are still around?
I told you I don't remember.
Ae Dulhain, where is my betel leaf?
Don't worry, I'll help you.
See this is the family photograph taken
during your grandfather's second wedding.
Is it?
Look at this one...
your elder grandma had 11 kids...
...and your younger grandma had 9.
Your father was your
younger grandma's 6th born.
Is it?
- Mirza...? come close.
- Uh... yeah.
Come closer.
Did you and I get married
or did I elope with you?
What are you saying, Begum!
Of course we got married.
I even paid you the traditional dues.
So who did I elope with?
That mongrel, Abdul Rehman.
Anyway.
Just tell me who all
are alive in your family.
You seem to be after my family.
No... no... all I'm asking is... just the
way your eldest sister is still alive...
...but your middle brother is dead...
...so what about your other brothers
and sisters...are they around or...?
Look I have not invited
anyone for the party.
Is it clear?
When Nehruji comes,
I'm going to complain about you...
...and make sure that
he puts you behind the bars.
These are all your family members only.
Your brothers. Your sisters.
Just think maybe there was a good news
that someone had passed away.
- I mean...
- What do you mean? Just get lost.
Fine... relax.
- Hey you... get me something to eat.
- Sure.
- Older sister is still alive...
- Old man is hanging
- ...younger brother is dead.
- To threads of a torn long coat
He is nearing death but he is not bothered
to change his mischievous ways
He is disliked by everyone,
but he is happy doing mischief
Huh! You wanted to nab my mansion...
there... now you come.
- Oh! this got left out.
- He wanders aimlessly around
- Let me see who enters.
- Every nook and corner
Old man is hanging to threads
of a torn long coat
Hey kids... get out... out!
He is nearing death but he is not bothered
to change his mischievous ways
What?
When did he put these locks?
There are more?!
What is going on...?
Saturn is of low...
...but do you see the mount of Venus?
- Everything is in these hands.
- Oh?
- Now you see...
- Shukla ji.
- Ya?
- It's me.
Sit.
I'll read your right palm
in the canteen... okay?
Yes?
You had come to my house...
without informing.
- I've no idea what you're talking about
- You'd had climbed the tree... my place.
And then you said to stay
in touch... Fatima Mahal.
Right... Now I remember... so...
What brings you here?
Bring me the files.
Sir... Remember I had mentioned to you about...
Fatima Mahal.
- Yeah?
- He's one of the tenants.
Rentals have gone miserably up
in Lucknow... better start looking out.
You let him know.
What is going on Shukla ji ...?
What are you intending to do?
Why is he asking me
to look for a new house?
And what have you spoken to Mirza ...?
Let's step out for a bit.
So she is not his mother?
No... his wife... 17 years older than him.
Ohh!
That toilet wall... I hope
you haven't got it repaired, right...?
Why are you after that wall?
You have any idea how difficult
it is getting for us to manage.
Shut up!
Do not raise your voice,
it is a government office.
Not Nixon market that you
yell and sell bargained clothes.
I speak only in favour of your case.
C'mmon.
Hit here...
on the wall.
Why?
Pcch... you ask too many questions.
Just do as I say.
Harder!
Did it collapse? No.
Because this is how
the house walls need to be.
Not like yours that one kick
and the entire building comes down.
Maybe we all tenants can
collect some money and repair it.
What about rest of the mansion?
Today it is just one wall...
tomorrow it'll be the roof.
Day after, the stairs.
Do you guys have the money?
But there are many people living
in such dilapidated buildings...
...your government doesn't go around
taking the responsibility of helping them.
Of course we don't... But we are taking
the responsibility of this mansion.
Because if this comes crashing down,
trust me you won't find a single body.
Let's go and grab some breakfast.
I'm quite full.
I am talking for myself.
Come on.
Musa Bagh...
Dilkusha palace...
Farhat Bakhsh palace...
Imam Bara Chota Bara...
Amin-ud-daula's Residency...
Asif-ud-daula's Residency...
Qaiser Bagh, Baradari...
Now if you notice these are all...
...historically important buildings.
Heritage.
Now look here.
Are you saying even trees
come under your authority?
Trees, plants, rivers, canals,
roads, buildings... everything.
Do you see this railing?
Are you restoring this building as well?
Oh no... not this useless building.
We were passing by, so just stopped.
How do you know all this, Shukla ji?
I am the government and
the government knows everything.
You know what my father says?
What?
That a man isn't rich
or poor because of his money.
But because of his intelligence.
And I'm beginning to feel that...
...you are not only poor
because of your money.
...but even because of a
total lack of intelligence.
As if you are very intelligent!
I'm not but at least I pretend to be.
And by pretending over a
period of time I will become.
What have I done now?
That man kept rattling off such
big names of the British and Nawabs...
...and you are such a nincompoop
that you stood quiet.
If I was there I would
have pinned him down.
And would have told him that I stay in
Fatima Mahal and not Taj Mahal.
So just stay away.
I was about to talk to mom about us.
I don't think I'm going to do that now.
Just because I called you nincompoop,
you got cheesed off.
Fine... they've selected a guy for me.
Should I say yes?
Don't bother calling
me for your wedding.
I'm not an idiot to waste my
father's hundred bucks per plate on you.
Stop clinging to me.
I'll drop you at the bus stop.
I'm not taking the bus nor am
I interested in clinging to you.
You picked me up from home,
so you better drop me back there.
New ones are for Rs.100 and
second hand ones are for Rs.25/-
Okay, give me Rs.20.
- Rs.20?
- Rs.20.
Just try and see if it fits.
Oh my god!
Aah! They're fine.
I'll keep my old ones.
Give me that other one.
Where did you learn all this?
I know all the hairstyles. See?
Show.
Ooh nice.
Where will you go looking this stunning?
Why should I tell?
But I'm certainly
not taking Mirza with me.
Oh that poor man will cry
so much... he'll die without you.
He'll do none of that.
Here... live all the tenants of Mirza.
This whole lane.
Begum's section is upstairs
and Mirza's downstairs.
Oh she's sitting downstairs today.
Greetings, Begum... how are you?
Greetings.
Do you recognise me?
Uh... mm... yeah.
If you've recognised me tell me my name.
You're...
Galileo!
Hey Pandey ji,
come over here, will you?
Why have you strung him along with you?
What do you mean strung along?
Are you calling me a bull
who can be tagged along anywhere?
Forget that, where are the papers?
Who's... what... papers?
Papers for this white elephant.
Papers of this property... my dear Uncle.
Ok, so I've figured out
the entire list of all the alive...
...and dead relatives, every little detail.
That was point number 2.
Point 1 is papers.
Who asked you to jump the order?
Point number 2 and then...
It's been days Pandey ji...
You seem to have dropped out of nowhere.
Ya... I guess it was time for me to.
Come... come...
Aah! This... point no.1.
I wasn't there during the day.
Nor me.
But you were there, Mishra ji!
But no one's ever
there during afternoons.
Whoever that chap was,
must have been a lawyer.
Must have been?
He was indeed a lawyer...
People are so naive in this house.
That chap had a black coat on his arm
and no one noticed... amazing!
Hey don't throw your knowledge
around here... it's ok.
I am throwing knowledge?
A man in a black coat,
he came, he saw and he went.
If you can apply your mind, so can I. OK?
Look here now.
Look... come here.
This is the mansion.
There is Mirza and then there is us.
The tenants.
Tenant Baankey... Dadda called
the archaeology department fellow.
Hey... I never called anyone.
Keep quiet! And don't interrupt now...
Guddo... you go on now, we're all ears.
This archeology department chap
has met Mirza as well.
And now Mirza has this
lawyer on his side too!!
Let me tell you what's
really happening here.
Archeology department, the lawyer
and Mirza, they're all on one side...
...and we, tenants have no one on our side.
What do you think I've been
trying explain for the longest time?
So, don't try to explain...
get out of here, you!
Very well!
Can't we get our own lawyer?
And how do you fathom
that will happen? For free?
"Can't we get a lawyer" hah!
Well... we can kiss
this mansion goodbye then.
It's not that simple to chuck us out.
Mirza's been at it... scheming
to chuck us out everyday...
...and our man is living in
a fool's paradise.
We've been living here for years, ok?!
We been paying rent regularly,
with receipts.
So what?
Won't let the mansion go.
As you can see, there's non stop digging
going on here for the past three days.
If indeed 1000 tonnes
gold is found here...
...today according to the saint's dream,
that will be India's...
That's right... four meters to the left.
Shukla ji... Shukla ji.
Increase the number of cranes...
Shukla ji.
What are you doing here?
Wait there.
Yes, tell me.
- Mirza's gone wild.
- What do you mean?
He's engaged a lawyer...
filed a case against us.
- That mansion is as good as gone
- That property ain't going nowhere.
He has no case.
Needn't worry as long as I am here.
I am no loser.
In fact I am the loser here.
While I am taking you around Lucknow,
you are meeting Mirza in private.
Oh come on... I'd met him once...
to survey the property...
...and you bloody well know about that!
So what was that lawyer
doing at the property then?
Don't boil my blood!
Look over there.
Some random saint had a dream about a
1000 tonnes of gold that's buried here...
...that's all it took to start
this manic digging.
Gold? So that's the mad rush all about.
Bullshit... There's nothing here.
But I got to do my job.
And do you see the media,
like hungry hyenas.
Anyway... did you have a word
with the tenants?
Just the way I'd told you to.
No.
For heaven's sake...
can you do that first...
...and let me handle this lawyer.
1000 tonnes of gold is a lot.
And you're getting none of it.
You look pretty... this way.
I'll be back in minute.
Where are you off to?
I said I am coming.
These papers are all I have.
Alright... that's point no. 1: papers.
Hmm.
And now point no 2...
...because your Begum
doesn't have a clear title...
...you'll have to procure
NOC from her relatives.
Where in the world will I find them...?
Well, you'll have to... come what may...
are you getting me?
'Cause if this property
is declared 'disputed'...
...then no force on earth can stop that
archeology fellow from entering it...
...and that's the end of your dream...
...to become the sole owner of that place.
Here... now for god sake
keep these papers safe.
I've let you in today.
If you ever come in after
the gates are locked...
...you can jolly well spend the rest
of the night outside the gate.
You know Mirza, you can't even
imagine where I've been today.
Really?
Where from?
Unnaao... A thousand tonnes
of gold is buried there.
Gold...?
Yeah and they are digging it up there.
It's a mad rush, unbelievable.
Hold on...
hold on... where are you off to?
Do you remember... 2 years back...
...they found two vaults buried in
an old mansion?
Yes...?
This place right here is a mansion too.
Old one at that.
But you wouldn't ever
dig up your own home... would you?
Obviously... not.
So... that's what got me late.
Put your ears to the ground.
Can you hear it?
Here.
Can your hear it?
Nothing?
What... where?
Found anything?
Gold...
Gold... gold.
Huh...
There's nothing inside... see.
Greed... Mirza?
Greed, is like slow poison.
It eats up a person from inside.
Look at yourself... lying on this cot...
...in a year or two you'll find
yourself lying in a coffin...
...if you don't stop this nonsense.
The truth is...
...firstly I haven't heard
of anyone dying of greed ever.
Got it?
And secondly... I am not greedy.
- You're not greedy?
- Not even an ounce.
So this episode of digging up
for gold in the burning heat...
...till you passed out, this behavior...
Doesn't it amount to greed?
You call that greed. I call it
my love for this mansion... immense love.
Unparalleled love.
And I can do anything for that love.
Look, Begum's been keeping unwell,
and you've taken to this bed now...
...have you ever thought of the future?
What will happen?
When?
You'll chuck us out, Begum's
not surviving another season...
...who's going to look after you
and your dilapidated mansion?
Have you ever thought about it?
And you're not getting any younger at 78.
Look at it this way.
You have no kids.
I have no father to look after.
Forget the whole lawyer, court mess...
And adopt me.
Get out of here... get out!
Get out of here, you termite!
I was giving some sound advice,
but you're not worth it.
But don't you ever try to uproot me.
I'm embedded here for good, got it?
Adopt me... huh!
Get out, you parasite!
Calls me a parasite, huh!!
And that sheet... That's mine...
when did you sneak that in, huh?
Your legendary crookery
...it'll never go away.
Sure keep it... take it away.
Just know that I've farted
on it the whole day.
Why've you got us here Baankey...
and why are these cannons here?
Because it's time now to attack.
What do you mean...?
Do you know who 'Asif-ud-daulla' was?
C'mmon they're from Lucknow...
of course they would've heard his name.
Of course.
So Asifudaulla's mom
was quite a dominating lady...
...she wouldn't let him be...
...where he goes...
who he meets... plays with...
...poor guy couldn't do
a thing without her approval...
...then one day,
Asif-ud-daulla just lost it...
...he said to hell with her
rules and regulations.
I am going to Lucknow.
He packed up his bags...
from Faizabad he moved to Lucknow...
...and look what a beautiful city he made.
And why are you telling us all this?
'Cause Asif-ud-daulla's mom
and this Mirza in our lives...
...they both are just the same.
Don't dry the pickles in the sun...
don't park the car there.
Why are the kids playing
in the courtyard...
...mend the wall yourself...
I don't have the money for the painting...
...if you come late
I won't let you in...
...for god sake...
I'm done with his do's and don't's.
Therefore, revolt!
If that damn Haveli
doesn't have place for such gentle...
...humble, peace loving tenants like us...
...it certainly can't belong to Mirza.
When did it ever belong to him?
But why should we vacate this place?
To enable the restoration work...
how will it happen otherwise?
Once the restoration is done...
...we'll request the ministry of art and
culture to commission a museum here...
...a place in history.
Sooner or later, we'll be served
a notice to vacate the house...
...it's a matter of
heritage property now.
But Shukla ji believes...
...we could definitely get an allotment
for a LIG house as a compensation.
That's if we go by Shukla ji's advice.
The government is bound
to provide compensation...
...where will you go otherwise...
...in case it's proven
to be a heritage property.
But its not proven yet,
so why are we jumping to conclusions?
That's why I said, "in case",
if you didn't hear me correctly...
...but we will prove it...
a heritage property.
What if we need a MIG accommodation?
We could try for one or two of them...
...but even the LIG is pretty good too.
There's a private toilet,
separate kitchen.
Think about it, ok?
Should we move ahead now?
Have you ever thought about
this dilapidated mansion?
What if it collapsed one day?
Your bodies will have to be hauled
out with the help of cranes...
...one limb at a time!
We need to go to Sitapur.
Take the bus headed from Qaisarbagh.
From Qaisarbagh?
Let's go then... to Qaisarbagh.
Passengers for Sitapur,
please move to Qaisarbagh.
A powerful man will
dance on drum's beat...
...like a monkey of juggler
when life plays its music.
A powerful man will dance
on drum's beat...
...like a monkey of juggler
when life plays its music.
In the mint of breath...
- He's been in this state for 15 years now.
- ...limited coins will sound.
Get it done.
Everybody...
...is stuck in the fake
net of love and illusion.
- Fatto bi... She's still alive?
- Like Searching fresh...
- She refuses to die!
- ...water in the ocean
A powerful
man will dance on drums beat...
Should we?
...like a monkey of juggler
when life plays its music.
Would you know how to get to lane no 3?
A powerful man will dance on drums beat...
- You're here to meet Jamila bano?
- ...like a monkey of juggler
- Yes.
- When life plays its music.
She passed away... this very morning.
Passed away?
You're a wee bit late.
The funeral procession has left already...
if you wish I could drop you there.
Oh no... don't bother really...
- Are your sure?
- Yes yes, sure.
- She's gone!!
- Yes, she's gone.
This one too.
This case got solved on its own!
Luxury will have a cost.
A pipkin of timber
can be fired only once
We broke all relations with Fatima aunt...
...the day she married this Mirza.
We have nothing to do
with him or his mansion.
Now you get out from here...
...and never bother
showing your face to us.
When a spiritual soul encountered...
- Just put your thump here... right here ... thank you.
- ...powerful man will dance on drum's beat.
Mirza...
I've been wondering...
what just happened in there.
Why do these guys hate you so much?
Really?
- No...?
- I never felt anything like that.
- Really?
- No.
I must have misheard.
Like searching for
fresh water in the ocean.
A powerful man
will dance on drum's beat...
...like a monkey of juggler
when life plays its music.
Stop here.
Here.
Desire... it can make
a man stoop really low.
I've 3 wonderful kids.
Fulfilling relationship with the wife.
And yet?
I am here with you in this room.
I feel I may not be able to do this.
Hope you won't judge me.
No.
I get it.
I mean if your kids
ever come to know that...
...their dad is up to
all this hanky panky stuff.
Won't be the best situation to be, no?
A kiss?
Maybe just a kiss?
That will do no harm.
Uhh... there is an issue there as well.
Why?
Uh... It's embarrassing...
but... I have Pyorrhoea.
Ok... let's cut the crap...
and get straight to the point.
This file has all the documents...
my mark sheet etc.
You'd mentioned about
the museum right...
...I can take good care of it.
I mean you just get me a job
in your dept. now.
Alright... alright...
I'll take care of it... you needn't worry.
Alright then.
Ok listen...
whatever that happened here...
...just keep it to yourself.
Are you mad? Of course.
You just saved yourself
a lifetime of guilt.
Just a second.
Brick from the latrine wall.
You'd said you would
use it for the research?
Oh... of course... thanks.
Uh... may I?
Yeah?
Go see a dentist.
Remember the other day I'd come...
that's when I plucked these.
From the mango tree in our mansion...?
Put it down!
To prove the historical
status of the mansion...
...not to make pickles from them.
Come here.
Look at this.
Brick?
It's from your latrine.
So why is it kept on a plate?
We're researching on it...
its shape... size... width... length...
...the sand it's made up of...
...basically to determine its age.
You haven't studied at all... right?
As if we had the money.
Your dad died while he was young...?
Some years back.
I took over the wheat mill since grade six.
Mummy was adamant to teach Neetu,
Payal, Guddo...
...so and since then
I've been grinding...for them.
You are also sad... hmm.
You need to reach a conclusion soon...
with this brick...
...'cause I can sense danger
lurking all over the mansion.
Look mister... work will
happen at its own pace...
...alright... just be thankful
that I got you here in the lab.
And by the way.
Guddo is an intelligent girl.
I'll take care of her... job.
Hey... stop.
- Get me to the court quickly.
- Stop... hey.
You carry on... just carry on.
I said stop... hold on.
What's with you, dude?
What?
We don't need to be a lawyer
to know the legal rights of a tenant.
Got it?
- Fine... but I am... Mirza's lawyer.
- Really?
...And your bullying
won't work with me...
...'cause grabbing someone's land
or property is not only illegal...
...but also a punishable crime.
But where have we grabbed it?
We are paying the rent.
Ya!
You call that rent?
What else?!
It's pittance.
Look at me, Mr Pittance.
Mind your language.
Whatever it may be,
but we are still paying it...
...therefore we have right to privacy...
...you can't just walk in and
out of our home at unearthly hours...
...you can't cut our water or electricity supplies...
right to basic need...
...even if we don't pay
the rent for months...
...right to repair fund...who do you think
should get that wall mended?
And what about the plastering and painting
and other maintenance?
Should I list out more rights?
Sir, even we can file
a case against you...
...that of exploitation...alright...?
Madam, since you've clearly
researched all this...
...am sure you've also heard
of the rights of a landlord...
...the damaged wall
that you're talking about...
...who do you think did that damage...?
So if you know what I mean...
...a case of damage of property
can be filed against you...
...and in no time you'd be
thrown out of your home.
Thrown out... hah... my foot!
Well... I'd say go for
out of court settlement.
Everyone will benefit.
Let's go.
Hold on... hold on.
You don't teach us
our benefits and loss.
You mind your own damn life.
Get this, you can't exploit us...
...but if you try to...
...we know how to play
this game of 'sending notices'.
Now leave.
You slapped right on that lawyer's face!
She's too good.
Welcome welcome.
Old. Very old... mansion.
Click photo... photo... yes yes...
Come on... come over.
Be careful of the goat poop.
Look at this wall.
It's so thick...
this house is very old...
...over 100 years at least.
The landlord is a poor man...
see this architecture...
...English, French...
very meticulous in design...
...see these arcs.
Shukla ji?
Ok... you just take photos there...
there... click... go go go.
Where did you herd these tourists from?
Students from abroad.
China, Hong Kong, Cambodia...
research, architecture students.
So you've invaded my house yet again,
without my permission.
It's an official visit.
Need to investigate.
Investigate?
Come... come... keep walking.
This old man thinks that government
is interfering his house.
But he does not know.
Very soon this house will
be declared national property.
Awwwww.
You go there... click there.
Do you even know how old this mansion is?
How many years back... huh?
Can't say... not very old.
Go on write it down... under the heading heritage,
approximately 100 years old.
It's definitely lesser than that.
The walls haven't been white washed...
That's why.
Don't act smart with me now...
this is for government records.
When did this railing break away?
Maybe a year or two back.
He is lying.
Outright... it's been in that
broken state since I was born.
I am lying?
Write it down... 50 years back.
Come... come.
And this whole area
belongs to Begum.
All of this...
include it in the antique items list.
Click photos of each
one of them... come on.
There's more trash
stored inside as well.
Really?
Trash... what trash... huh?
Listen now.
Enough of this nonsense...
out from here now... out!
Yes yes we are leaving.
Yes, leave now!
I am warning you!
Mirza!
Get out! Leave now.
I am warning you...
don't you touch me... Mirza.
Hah! Don't touch me, he says.
I will get an official
letter the next time.
What letter are you talking about?
And how and with who's permission
are you selling this mansion?
- What do you mean?
- Selling it off... really?
Up until yesterday,
you were conniving with...
...the lawyer and filing
a case against us tenants...
- ...now you're selling it off?!
- Oh hold on... he can't sell.
It's my mansion my land, my will...
...I'll sell it as I wish, whosoever to...
You can, but not without our permission.
Permission... what permission,
what's this permission nonsense.
Permission... which I will never grant.
What do you mean?
Let the fun begin!
Permission.
Won't give permission! Huh!
Mansion...
That's one good thing you did...
...letting Gyanesh know that
you're selling the property.
Sit.
I just said what I had to at that point...
...but in reality...
I don't want to sell the mansion.
Firstly, we need a power of attorney
in your name.
For that we'll need Begum's
signature or a thumb impression.
I don't think she will be able
to recollect her signature...
...thumb impression.
That I'll ensure... but after that,
the mansion will be in my name, right?
Of course... mansion will be yours,
but only after Begum's death.
Here... get her signature
here at the bottom.
...or else her thumb
impression for sure.
Ok.
- Mirza, tea?
- No, you carry on.
Look at this mess?
It's on all my fingers.
But not this hand?
Don't worry...
we'll wash it... do you want some tea?
- What's this?
- Huh?
The thumb print you asked for...
what else?
It's all wrong.
I asked you to get a
left hand thumb impression...
...you've got the right hand one!
What's wrong now?
Am ok...
Am ok.
If the power of attorney
papers aren't done...
...you can forget about
your beloved mansion.
Here comes Mirza.
How are you, Begum?
It's ok.
Like I was saying...
...let bygones be bygones...
...we'll leave things the way
they were... like always...
Baankey can stay...
...I can talk to Christopher...
he will withdraw the case and sir...
...all the investigations
that you're conducting...
...all that can also stop... what say...?
Look Mirza,
this ship has now sailed too far...
...the mansion has been
documented in our records...
...and there is no turning back.
Oh... but.
- Let me show you something.
- Huh?
You should see how
our department works...
...you will feel proud too.
This is our lab.
Everything is done
very meticulously here...
...with minute detailing...
all these are antiques.
Do you have an idea how much
it costs in London... America?
Yes... all that is fine
but what about my mansion?
Again that mansion!
That's all you can think of.
Do you know how
much that mansion costs?
You'll lose your sense... if I tell you.
No... I mean... I don't know... how much?
How much do you think it's worth?
Its worth... it's priceless!
But... Its monetary value?
Priceless.
Uh... oh...?
Come.
Some things in life are so invaluable that
you cannot put a number to their worth...
...for eg. a mother's love...
Begum's love... in your case...
How invaluable it is...
but can you put a number to it?!
Similarly, your mansion...
priceless.
Oh no no no... hold on, hold on.
I am ok... uh... don't worry... am ok.
- What did you say... priceless?
- Yes... absolutely priceless.
So what's his problem if I went
and met that lawyer, Christopher?
Why is he creating such a ruckus...
and it's not that I went alone.
Alone? Didn't you go alone
to meet Gyanesh?!
Since the day she's
stopped oiling her hair...
...it's evident what all is
she up to...it's all clear.
- Baankey... I'm coming over.
- Hmm
Not that anyone's complaining about you...
...but you've been acting
footloose nowadays.
I don't care.
...I'd gone to get a job done...
that's all...
Exactly my point...
why are you meddling in between?
Why are you interfering?
'Cause I don't think you're capable
of doing this by yourself.
All you're doing is being
Gyanesh's lapdog...
...he promised an LIG flat
and you fell for it...
...while I'm talking about a proper flat...
if not here... then a backup.
Well... Guddo's making sense.
Ok then! Listen to her.
I am out of this, mom...
Don't come to me for anything.
Just look at him, mom...
look at him... he's just jealous.
Truth is he can't handle
the fact that I have gone and...
...done something productive on my own.
Brother... you go ahead and do your
own thing... I'll manage everything...
...mom, the house
and these two as well...
...you can just go
and romance that Fauzia.
Who's this Fauzia now?
No one... just don't bother.
Are you getting married to her?
Brother, you can romance
Fauzia on the terrace.
Just like Guddo... she romances
many boys behind the water tank.
Guddo?
What happened? Begum? She's not well?
Uh... well... You look somewhat sad?
Can't say anything at this moment.
She's not going to make it, is it?
Or...?
Can't say anything at this moment.
The disease is such that...
everything is...
So it's time for...?
Can't say anything at this moment.
- You should be prepared...
- No... no I get it... I understand.
- My fees?
- Fees?
That's all I have on me...
you may leave.
Hey... who got him here?
- No... no you go inside.
- Why did you get him here?
- Go inside... to Begum.
- How did you just walk in like that?
Why don't you go inside to the Begum...
Oh... I see.
You can't see her
in so much pain... hmm.
- Get him out of here.
- I swear you're worse than a devil.
Don't call me that... I'm no devil...
I'm telling you again, ok?
Get out of my way.
So Mirza... tell me.
I need a shroud.
- Shroud?
- Yesss...
- Is it the Begum?
- Why don't you show me one huh?
When did she pass away?
- How much is it for?
- Rs.150...
Can you show me something cheaper?
Mirza... have a little shame... huh?
You can't be negotiating at this hour?
Here... take it, that's all I have.
Why are you packing so many flowers?
I'm not decorating my house...
here keep them back.
That far... huh?
Begum's mother, her dad...
they're all buried in the mansion.
And you want to burry Begum here?
The farther she is from the mansion...
the better...
...she'll fit in this little space.
Even after she's dead...
if she remains stuck in the mansion...
...what's the point then?
But you'll have to pay.
Hmm... you get the ground ready...
I'm getting her here.
I'll pay you then... now move.
You're looking beautiful
Begum... come... quick.
Begum} Thanks,
I'm seeing you after many days myself.
Dulhain} Come this way, Begum.
Oh! This vulture is back?
Where to?
She's been really beat because of her illness...
I'll take her out for a walk.
We'll also look up the doctor
on our way back... I
Let me look for tempo.
- Go quickly... and look for one.
- Yes yes.
Let's go.
Our Begum... she really cares for you.
She's got your favourite
cotton candy... try some.
Have it... and go to sleep now.
- So here is the blueprint.
- Blueprint.
It's a fifteen floor building...
12 floors here and 3 on this side.
They'll all be next to each other?
Yes next to each other
but 12 floors tall!!
Mirza's here!!! What should I do?
- Sit, keep seated.
- Should I leave?
You've been appointed, my dear.
Come Mirza... come join us.
Her? She's Guddo.
Why have you called her?
She is an expert in legal language.
I've kept her as my assistant.
Come and sit.
Look at this... is it alright?
Very good.
Correct. Sit.
She's very helpful.
We've solved the case.
Look Guddo, the real villain
in your life is not Mirza...
...and Mirza,
your tenants aren't the villains either.
It's that conniving, meddling...
Gyanesh from archaeology
And what's the logic here?
What do you mean?
If this case reaches the civil court...
...it will take at least
6 to 8 months to resolve.
So the longer it drags...
The longer we can stay, isn't it?
Common Guddo, you should know better.
Gyanesh has his personal
interest in the mansion...
...that's why he is chasing this issue...
...the day he gets his hands
on some solid evidence...
...2 months is all it will
take... and you will be thrown out...
- 2 months... that's all?
- 2.
Ohh!
So Mirza...
I have a suggestion...
...before Gyanesh makes his move...
...there's only one option left...
...just sell the mansion.
- Hmm... I get it now.
- What?
If we sell the mansion,
we'll get something in hand...
...and if the government
takes over... we'll get zilch.
Correct!
You got it!
You know that builder... Mun Mun ji.
He's shown a lot of interest...
in the mansion... I know him personally.
We'll sort everything in a week or two.
I've spoken to him personally...
he's a very famous builder.
Gyanesh... that crook won't
last in front of him... am telling you.
Have you understood?
Have you got the papers now...
or you just sauntered in aimlessly?
What about the money...
when can we get that?
Can you get the papers in place first?
This isn't a flea market...
we're not selling trinkets here.
- Guddo?
- One second.
Really Mirza...
your status is no less than a beggar.
No illegal talking please.
We're talking about millions here.
We must have a proper deal in place...
I am very clear about it.
Ok... ok... ok.
Thank you.
Guddo, file these duplicates please.
Hello hello... yes... Sinha you bugger,
why is it taking so much time?
Uncle... few formalities are left.
You can consider it done...
Gyanesh... tell him.
Uncle it's like this... the bricks of
the mansion aren't exactly...
...the pristine antique ones like in
the historical Imambara...
...but I can tell you that it's the
typical British / French structure ones...
...matches perfectly with it...about 20%.
So it's done then...
go get the report ready.
Just one more thing, Uncle.
There's an old mango tree there...
we're in talks with the forest dept...
...we're figuring out its age...
the variety of the plant?
Even the mango tree is witness to the
historical importance of the mansion...
...then why are we dithering so much, Sinha?
Look, I am not in power right now...
...so no media's going to
really pay attention to me...
...let's wrap this up quickly...
- What date is it today?
- 29th.
Great... so let's get this sorted by
15th august... get the property sealed...
...and it should be livable
in about a year.
Uncle... you plan to...
stay in the mansion?
Who's this chap?
And why is he calling me uncle?
That mansion has a lot of tenants..
Uncle... he's one of them.
Alright... ok.
Give him some space
in the servant quarters...
...that are being constructed
behind the mansion.
- Alright.
- Ok.
See you.
Get the bricks tested
in the lab... real quick.
Alright... got it.
I'm not going to stay
in the servant quarters.
Listen you... just accept
what you're being offered...
...else you'll end up
with nothing at all.
These are called the LIG flats!
- Sir is busy.
- You can go in now.
Ok.
North facing and south...
they're both equally.
This better not be a bogus case
like the last time?
Not at all... this time we've got
all the papers in place...
...there's a duplicate copy...
right outside.
Do you need any help... kidnapping?
No... no no.
- Need goons?
- Not required...
You know the Begum...
she won't be around for too long.
And then Mirza... he's a dimwit...
the one sitting outside.
Mirza's sitting outside?
What's with you?
Get up and sit properly.
When is the deal happening...?
Max... Two to three days.
Let's do it in two days.
2 days... sounds doable.
What about my commission?
Just shut up... commission, my foot.
Mun Mun ji...
he maybe a big shot builder.
But am no less... I told him very clearly...
Mirza is my closest buddy.
I won't take him for a ride.
He asked me what should we do?
I told him to organise
the advance quickly.
Now?, he asked.
He really respects me.
I said take your time.
The moment Mirza hands over the
original papers... you pay the advance.
Now, you get the original papers,
as soon as you can.
I'll organise the bulldozer.
Like Now? Where will we go?
Not like right now Ms. Guddo...
Let's first get the advance.
- How much money will I get?
- 5% share.
How much would that be?
Rs, 500,000/-
Get the papers ready...
I'll begin at my end too.
Come on, Guddo.
Mirza... you're forgetting your file.
One... ten... hundred... thousand...
one hundred thousand.
Five hundred thousand!!!
That's five hundred thousand?!
Mirza... are you alright?
Huh?...one...
Should we drop you home?
Ten... Hundred...
Five hundred thousand!
You come from dust,
and to dust you shall return.
Five hundred thousand!
You come from dust,
and to dust you shall return.
All I am saying is that be it LIG...
or an apartment...
...we'll stay together only wherever we go.
Have you ever wondered
about this fragile body?
The Gurus shed light,
but you could never comprehend.
Start stop, start stop,
the rhythms of breath
And when it does stop, what would
you have lost, what would you have gained?
You come from dust,
and to dust you shall return.
Dear friend...
You come from dust,
and to dust you shall return
Let Baankey talk.
That's the first property deed...
...and this is the second one,
after increased rent...
- ...these are the receipts.
- Okay.
Let's show all these papers to Baankey.
- Everyone's ready?
- Yes.
- And papers are in place?
- By when will they be here?
They'll be here... ok?
Ya... right here.
- This way sir.
- Sir, may I put up the board?
Once I'm done with
reading the notice, then.
I really look forward to this part
of my job...
- One of you cops come with me.
- Ok sir.
This way sir...
Those guys are here, Baankey.
This way sir.
Mom... they are here...
- Do you see this place, sir?
- Hello.
I'm presuming everyone is here... come...
Yeah we're all here...
and ready...
Come, let's go.
MIRZA CHUNNAN NAWAB, are you...?
As if you didn't know my name.
Give me the notice.
Pay attention here.
This is an official notice.
After using and completing various
scientific methods of investigations...
...we, the archaeology department,
have come to a conclusion...
...that this 100 year
old mansion is not only...
...dangerous for the
habitants of this place...
...but is of an extreme
historical importance as well.
Therefore keeping in mind its possible
social and cultural contribution...
...we hereby declare that all the tenants
vacate this mansion at the earliest.
- By order.
- What is he saying, Baankey?
We have to leave? Where will we go?
What about our rights?
Wait I am asking... wait...
can you guys... shut up... I am talking!
Mr.Shukla, I went around
the whole town with you, for this?
Is this how you pay us back?
What about the LIG-MIG
apartments you had promised us?
Or was it part of your deceit plan?
Hand over the official notice to him
and put up the board outside.
I've no interest in this drama.
Drama?
Is this drama?
What the hell are you saying?
Shut up all of you.
You committed for LIG
MIG accommodation for us.
Why is it missing in the notice?
Why isn't it mentioned here?
We want it in writing.
Where do you reckon we'll go from here?
And what about this Mirza?
Why would he go anywhere...
he's the owner...
I get it... he's the owner so he stays...
And we're thrown out...
...and we...we are the doofus dogs
who fell for the bone you showed us...
...if I could throttle you just now.
You can't deny us those LIGs.
Put that stick away.
LIG comes under another department...
not mine...
But you never mentioned that earlier.
It's not as if we're
asking you to vacate now.
2 months notice is a good period.
Not good enough to find
a new accommodation!
No no... these pests can not
infest my mansion anymore...
And you guys leave too.
I've already sold off this mansion to
Mun Mun ji builders... so go...
And Christopher made it
all happen... now do you get it...?
We'll get a flat.
How can you sell it...?
It's utter rubbish...
Say what you may...
this place is sold!
Salute, sir.
We have thoroughly researched
this property, we are entitled...
Hey move... give way...
Mun Mun ji is here...
- Sir this way.
- Ah good job, Christopher.
- We'll have a garden here.
- Ok.
- And parking up to 3 floors.
- Very nice.
- You've really done superb this time around.
- Thank you.
- We can build up to 25 floors at least.
- Hold on... hold on.
You can't construct any building here.
This mansion is getting sealed.
- They are from archaeology department.
- Yeah that's ok you can seal it for now...
...once our cranes and bulldozer arrive,
we'll remove that seal.
- Sinha sir.
- You guys are not getting it...
...you can not construct a building
here, neither now nor in the future...
...we will be locking the gates.
Yes that's a good idea.
Christopher, once they put the locks,
take the keys from them.
Sure sir.
Yes mummy, I'll get the peas.
Take a picture for the records.
- I am Mirza!
- Click!
What is going on?!
Move away.
- What is going on...?
- Who's he?
- Existing Tenant...
- Tenant?!
Accountant, give him some cash.
Ok sir.
Give them a few bundles.
Oh yes... this we deserve.
- Please come in line.
- Just buy them out...
This is ours... not charity.
Why are you paying them...
this money is mine.
It's ours.
Look at this hyena... stealing my money.
I sold the mansion... my money.
How is it yours?!
Begum left us.
She's gone.
Begum's Gone!
What, what happened to her?
Begum's dead?
Who's Begum now?
Fatima Begum...
the owner of this mansion...
She's dead... so now?
It had to happen one day.
Now? Papers...?
Of this mansion?
All that must be in place.
We'll get them now.
Begum's gone... as in...?
As in gone... she's gone... Forever...
When...?
Three days back...
right in middle of the night.
Why didn't you tell me then?
Telling you now...
following her command.
Look there...
What happened, Baankey?
Tell us what's going on!
She's gone.
Is that her will?
Yes... her will.
Dear Mirza...
By the time you get this letter,
I'd be gone... far away.
Along with the actual documents...
...I've sold this mansion to Abdul
Rehman for a sum total of one rupee.
And will be with him, now on.
Sold off the mansion... as in...?
Begum isn't dead...
she has eloped.
What...?
Begum has eloped... she isn't dead.
What happened, Baankey?
What's wrong with Begum?
Begum is alive and has
eloped with her old lover.
- Eloped?
- Really?
With Abdul Rehman...
Begum?!
Mrs. Mishra! someone help...
Eloped... at this age?
What now, Shukla...?
Where will we go now?
Let's have a cup of tea.
Tea?
- Christopher.
- Sir!
One rupee!
You're offering a stash of money.
- I want this Abdul Rehman.
- Sure sir.
I knew it all along.
Good on her... wolves like you all
need to be treated this way.
Ruined... forever!
That day when you kept
inquiring about my family...
...you reminded me of the love
Abdul Rehman had for me.
While I always had an inkling
of your malicious intent...
...that day I became certain that you
wanted to nab my grand father's property...
...and were just waiting for me to die.
I broke Abdul Rehman's heart
and married you...
...because of my love
for this mansion...
...for I was born here.
On one side he wanted me to leave
all this and go to London with him...
...and here you,
you were ready to be a house husband.
This mansion was my weakness.
So I put my trust on you... my mistake
I knew all along that you were
responsible for all the petty thefts.
But I never interfered because
our house expenses were taken care of.
Move aside.
I am getting the gas cylinder...
We're taking it to the van...
Take this as well...
I'll take it, keep it here...
Let's go...
Well I always imagined that after me,
it'll be you who'll acquire this mansion...
...but when I realized that
you wanted to sell off the mansion...
...I decided to take
matters in my hand...
...and sold off the place.
May god be by your side...
Please do not touch anything...
it's all sold.
Though you aren't a bad man at heart...
...but no one can say when
the devil inside may take over...
...therefore all the legal proceedings
will be done by my lawyer...
...whom you may have seen
earlier as my doctor.
Now I am at ease that my mansion
will remain as is... untouched...
Shall we?...I need to put the locks...
Also, just as a small token
for all that you did for this mansion...
I am leaving behind
your favourite chair...
...and my two bedroom
Hussain Gunj house in your name.
Do let me know if you'll be sending me the
divorce paper or should I send them to you?
God bless. Forever yours, Fatto.
- I'll be back in a moment...
- Sure.
Excuse me, do you have organic flour...?
Doesn't seem like this shopkeeper would
have ever heard the word organic...
Let's go to the mall...
Useless!
Mirza... will you take us to the market?
- Baba... will you...?
- Sure... sit...
You've lost so much weight
Thank you so much
Hi, how are you?
Hello... this is a private property...
where do you think you're going?
What's going on inside...?
Remember that old lady who
used to stay here... Fatima Begum...
It's her birthday celebration.
She's here.
Look at all these
VIP guests who've come.
If you want to see... stand
behind the gates.
Get away now.
Happy birthday to you!
It's all over Mirza... go home...
The battle is set. The lines are drawn
Seething in anger,
Gulabo fights,
Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
Grabbing at necks
Chokeholds and hooks
Over candies and cake. Any excuse
they'll make seething in anger,
Yeah, Gulabo fights,
Oh yeah, Sitabo fights.
Gulabo fights,
How much did you sell that chair for?
Rs.250...
Begum was 15 years elder to you,
wasn't she?
What did you see in her...?
The mansion!
I only saw the mansion.
And what the hell
did Begum see in you...?
My youth.
This is a fair of two days only...
This is a fair of two days
only and then the game is over.
Life is about come and go,
life is about moving ahead.
Sweet and kind words are that treasure
which pours like honey...
...and like those prints
which can never be erased.
Life is about come and go,
life is about moving ahead.
Oh dear, we are like a pot of mud
and will return to mud one day.
Life is about come and go,
life is about moving ahead.
Life is about moving ahead.
There are lots of
stories flowing in the air...
...with so much of innocence
and mischievousness.
There are solid colors of
morning and evening together...
...there are worships, adhan together,
with the purpose of pray.
Here every house's rooftop has
the food and water for birds too...
...such is our philosophy.
Life is about come and go,
life is about moving ahead.
Life is about moving ahead.
Life is about come and go,
life is about moving ahead.